conservice.com 2019-07-02

# 

####  Privacy Policy

##### Last updated May 2018

This privacy policy details Conservice’s policies and practices regarding our collection, use, and disclosure of personally identifiable information by us, our affiliates, and subsidiaries. By using our products, services, and websites, you consent to our collection and disclosure practices as outlined below. 

#### Information Collected

Conservice may collect various types of information through our services and websites. Through our contractual agreement with your Residence, certain personally identifiable information has been provided to us including your name, the names of any co-residents, and residential address. This information can be found on your monthly billing statement. By using our website to gain access to information, including your billing statements, you agree to provide certain personally identifiable information (such as an email address and account number) that will allow us to identify your account and authorize access. We also collect information provided by you to respond to any customer service inquiries, including email address and phone number. In order to process payments for outstanding balances, we will collect your credit or debit card number, zip code, and other verification information. You may make changes to your personally identifiable information through your website portal or by calling our customer service department at 1-866-947-7379. 

#### Disclosure of Information

Any information shared with us will be used solely for the purpose it was shared for. Conservice does not license, share, or sell information to third-parties for marketing purposes. We may disclose your information to third-parties in the following circumstances: 

(1) To comply with any applicable legal or regulatory requirement, including subpoenas or similar legal process; (2) To protect against fraudulent, abusive, unauthorized, or unlawful use of Conservice’s products, services and websites; (3) To protect our rights or property; and (4) In some instances, we contract with third-party companies to perform services for us, which include mailing billing statements and processing credit card transactions. 

#### Children’s Online Privacy

Our products, services, and websites are not intended for use by children under the age of 13.

Privacy Policy Changes We reserve the right to update our privacy policy as necessary. We recommend you review this privacy policy periodically for any changes. The most recent version of this privacy policy will supersede all previous versions. 

#### Arbitration Agreement

By agreeing to be bound by this Privacy Policy, you agree that any and all legal claims or disputes arising between you and us (collectively “the Parties”) shall be resolved exclusively through mandatory, final, binding arbitration. Additionally, you agree to waive your right to a jury trial or to participate as a class member in a class action lawsuit or consolidated class action arbitration proceeding. The Parties agree the American Arbitration Association (“AAA”) shall conduct any arbitration involving a legal claim or dispute between them under its consumer rules as modified by this Privacy Policy. You may view these rules at www.adr.org. The place of arbitration shall be in the County of Salt Lake City, Utah, United States. 

If you intend to seek arbitration, you must first send us a Notice of Dispute (“Notice”) by email or using the contact function. Your Notice should include the following information: 

  * Your name
  * Your email and phone number
  * Your physical mailing address
  * The nature of the dispute with us
  * Any supporting documentation
  * The relief you are seeking

We shall review the Notice within 30 days. If 30 days passes from the date of receipt without resolution, either Party may move forward with arbitration. The Parties agree they shall be responsible for their own attorneys’ fees and shall equally share the cost of arbitration. 

#### Contact Us

If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policy, you can contact our customer service department at 1-866-947-7379.
